dealwiki.net 2017-07-22

# Privacy Policy

Dealwiki.net takes your privacy very seriously. Our privacy statement reflects the various measures we have taken to protect your privacy. Our web server collects visitors IP address and browsers version.

If you have elected to receive our free newsletter, your email-id is collected. This information is only used to provide you newsletter and important Dealwiki.net communication. We do not share any information with any other party. User may "unsubscribe" to newsletter by click on unsubscribe link in the newsletter.

Apart from this, we do not collect any other information about visitors. The information we collect, if any, is not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes.

Cookies: We set cookies to gather user specific information. We partner with some of the third party statistics provider who may set cookie to identify statistics such as unique visitors, visits etc.

In order to provide you best information about deals, We do provide advertisements and links to various retailers. Dealwiki.net has no control or knowledge about privacy policy of each retailer. Please see web site of retailers or contact them directly if you want any information about their privacy policy.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.

We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us via email at info@Dealwiki.net.

We can be reached via e-mail at info@Dealwikinet. If you have any questions or concerns, please feel free to email us the same email address.
